import 'package:flutter/material.dart';

// ignore: non_constant_identifier_names
List<Map<String, dynamic>> QuestionBank = [
  {
    'id': 1,
    'question': "1. Who created Flutter?",
    'A': 'Microsoft',
    'B': 'Google',
    'C': 'Adobe',
    'D': 'Facebook',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.orange,
  },
  {
    'id': 2,
    'question': "2.Which programing language is used by Flutter",
    'A': 'Ruby',
    'B': 'Dart',
    'C': 'C++',
    'D': 'Kotlin',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.purple,
  },
  {
    'id': 3,
    'question':
        "3. In 2014,on which ground did India win a test match after 28 years?",
    'A': 'The oval',
    'B': 'Bristol',
    'C': 'MCG',
    'D': 'Lord’s',
    'answer': 'D',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.lightGreen,
  },
  {
    'id': 4,
    'question':
        "4.Which of these animals is the largest member of the dog family?",
    'A': 'Jackal',
    'B': 'Hyena',
    'C': 'Wolf',
    'D': 'Fox',
    'answer': 'C',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.blue,
  },
  {
    'id': 5,
    'question':
        "5.The potato is believed to have been originated in which of these places?",
    'A': 'South America',
    'B': 'Asia',
    'C': 'Europe',
    'D': 'Africa',
    'answer': 'A',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.redAccent,
  },
  {
    'id': 6,
    'question':
        "6. What is the name of the revolver specially designed for women by Ordnance Factory Kanpur in 2014?",
    'A': "Damini",
    'B': 'Jyoti',
    'C': 'Jagriti',
    'D': 'Nirbheek',
    'answer': 'D',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.pinkAccent,
  },
  {
    'id': 7,
    'question':
        "7.In which of the following events will the fastest person win?",
    'A': 'Marathon',
    'B': 'Diving',
    'C': 'Weightlifting',
    'D': 'Shot Put',
    'answer': 'A',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.grey,
  },
  {
    'id': 8,
    'question':
        "8.What is the main ingredient of Kulcha in Matar Kulcha or Chole Kulcha?",
    'A': 'Daal',
    'B': 'Maida',
    'C': 'Besan',
    'D': 'Suji',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.red.shade800,
  },
  {
    'id': 9,
    'question':
        "9.Which aspect about a person is known by the words ‘natkhat’ and ‘manmauji’?",
    'A': 'Height',
    'B': 'Nature',
    'C': 'Skin colour',
    'D': 'Marital status',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.amber,
  },
  {
    'id': 10,
    'question':
        "10. In which of these sports are the terms reverse swing and reverse sweep used?",
    'A': 'Football',
    'B': 'Cricket',
    'C': 'Badminton',
    'D': 'Tennis',
    'answer': 'B',
    'backgroundColor': Colors.indigo,
  },
];
